<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- ~ Copyright (c) 2013 Development Gateway. ~ All rights reserved. This program and the accompanying materials ~ are made 
	available under the terms of the GNU Public License v3.0 ~ which accompanies this distribution, and is available at ~ http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl.html -->

<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
	<entry key="44typeOfRepayment.label">44. Type of repayment</entry>
	<entry key="44typeOfRepayment.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="44typeOfRepayment.help">1=equal principal payments (see glossary for explaination)
		2=annuity;
		3=lump sum;
		5=other;
	</entry>
	<entry key="44typeOfRepayment.help.detail">Field no. 44 - Type of repayment: The terms of repayment may be the following: 1= Equal principal
		payments (EPP) denotes a fixed schedule of equal instalments of principal
		adding up to the face value of the loan.
		Interest is charged on outstanding principal and the amount of individual service
		payments decreases with each payment
		of principal.
		2= In the annuity method, each service payment is established as an equal amount, within which the
		interest component
		declines with time while the principal component increases. 3= Lump sum means the loan is repaid in
		a single amount
		(principal and interest) at maturity. If interest is paid at various earlier dates, then the repayment
		schedule is a
		particular case of equal principal payments and should be reported under that category. 5= If the type of
		repayment
		does not correspond to any of the three above, use the code "other"
	</entry>

	<entry key="45numberOfRepayments.label">45. Number of Repayments per annum</entry>
	<entry key="45numberOfRepayments.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="45numberOfRepayments.help">1=annual
		2=semi-annual;
		4=quarterly;
		12=monthly
	</entry>
	<entry key="45numberOfRepayments.help.detail">Field no. 45 - Number of repayments per annum: 1=annual; 2=semi-annual; 4=quarterly; 12=monthly</entry>

	<entry key="46interestRate.label">46. Interest Rate</entry>
	<entry key="46interestRate.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="46interestRate.help">Enter: in 5 digits, e.g. "05200" for 5.2 % ; or
		"0" if interest free. If ODA loan with variable
		interest rate, report the variable rate in field 46 (e.g. LIBOR6M-1.5%)
		and the reference
		fixed rate in field 47.
	</entry>
	<entry key="46interestRate.help.detail">Field no. 46 - Interest rate: Enter in 5 digits, e.g. "05200" for 5.2 % ; or "0" if interest free.
		Most loans have a single interest rate which applies throughout the life of the loan. Enter this rate, including in it
		any charges in addition to the interest that are payable on the disbursed balance over the life of the loan. If ODA
		loan with variable interest rate, report the variable rate in field 46 (e.g. LIBOR6M-1.5%) and the reference fixed
		rate in field 47. Where interest is waived during the grace period (i.e. the interval between the commitment date and
		the first repayment date), report the loan as having two interest rates with zero interest being charged for the grace
		period. Loans with variable interest rates may only be classified as ODA if concessionality is guaranteed by a
		specific mechanism. The mechanism needs to ensure that the variable rate is concessional and that it will be capped so
		that the grant element over the life of the loan is at least 25%. To understand how the mechanism works read
		paragraphs 52 to 56 of the CRS++ guidliens available at
		http://www.oecd.org/dac/stats/documentupload/DCD-DAC(2013)15-FINAL-ENG.pdf
	</entry>

	<entry key="47secondInterestRate.label">47. 2nd Interest Rate</entry>
	<entry key="47secondInterestRate.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="47secondInterestRate.help">"Enter
		in 5 digits, e.g. "05200" for 5.2 % ; or
		"0" if interest free.
		If ODA loan with variable interest
		rate, report the variable rate in field 46 (e.g. LIBOR6M-1.5%) and the reference
		fixed rate in field 47. "
	</entry>
	<entry key="47secondInterestRate.help.detail">Field no. 47 - Second interest rate: Enter in 5 digits, e.g. "05200" for 5.2 % ; or "0" if interest
		free. Most loans have a single interest rate which applies throughout the life of the loan. Enter this rate, including
		in it any charges in addition to the interest that are payable on the disbursed balance over the life of the loan. If
		ODA loan with variable interest rate, report the variable rate in field 46 (e.g. LIBOR6M-1.5%) and the reference fixed
		rate in field 47. Where interest is waived during the grace period (i.e. the interval between the commitment date and
		the first repayment date), report the loan as having two interest rates with zero interest being charged for the grace
		period. Loans with variable interest rates may only be classified as ODA if concessionality is guaranteed by a
		specific mechanism. The mechanism needs to ensure that the variable rate is concessional and that it will be capped so
		that the grant element over the life of the loan is at least 25%. To understand how the mechanism works read
		paragraphs 52 to 56 of the CRS++ guidliens available at
		http://www.oecd.org/dac/stats/documentupload/DCD-DAC(2013)15-FINAL-ENG.pdf
	</entry>

	<entry key="48firstRepaymentDate.label">48. 1st RepaymentDate</entry>
	<entry key="48firstRepaymentDate.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="48firstRepaymentDate.help">First repayment rate</entry>
	<entry key="48firstRepaymentDate.help.detail">Field no. 48 - First repayment rate: State the dates at which the first and the final repayments of
		principal are due. Where the repayment schedule depends on the date(s) at which disbursements are made, please provide
		approximate repayment dates. Estimation might be based on the standard terms of repayment applied to a given recipient
		country or country group.
	</entry>

	<entry key="49finalRepaymentDate.label">49. Final repayment date</entry>
	<entry key="49finalRepaymentDate.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="49finalRepaymentDate.help">Final repayment date</entry>
	<entry key="49finalRepaymentDate.help.detail">Field no. 49 - Final repayment date: State the dates at which the first and the final repayments of
		principal are due. Where the repayment schedule depends on the date(s) at which disbursements are made, please provide
		approximate repayment dates. Estimation might be based on the standard terms of repayment applied to a given recipient
		country or country group.
	</entry>

	<entry key="50interestReceived.label">50. Interest Received</entry>
	<entry key="50interestReceived.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="50interestReceived.help">During the reporting year (full amount). DO NOT enter a negative amount.</entry>
	<entry key="50interestReceived.help.detail">Field no. 50 - Interest received: Interest received corresponds to the amount of interest and/or other
		charges received from the borrowing country, including payments to expunge or reduce interest due or in arrears.</entry>

	<entry key="51principalDisbursed.label">51. Principal Disbursed and still outstanding</entry>
	<entry key="51principalDisbursed.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="51principalDisbursed.help">The amount of principal owed on the loan at the end of the reporting year (full amounts)</entry>
	<entry key="51principalDisbursed.help.detail">Field no. 51 - Principal disbursed and still outstanding: Loans should be reported on the CRS++ until
		no outstanding principal or interest remains, regardless of whether the agency continues to extend new loans. Report
		under field 51. Principal disbursed and still outstanding the amount of principal owed on the loan at the end of the
		reporting year.
	</entry>

	<entry key="52arrearsOfPrincipals.label">52. Arrears of Principals (included in field 51)</entry>
	<entry key="52arrearsOfPrincipals.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="52arrearsOfPrincipals.help">At the end of the year (in full amount)</entry>
	<entry key="52arrearsOfPrincipals.help.detail">Field no. 52 - Arrears of principal (included in field 51): Report separately any arrears of
		principal and interest at the end of the reporting year, taking into account debt
		service payments received during the year (amortisation under field 35 and interest received under field 50), and including
		arrears that have arisen during the reporting year. Arrears of principal are part of the principal owed on the loan
		and should be included in the amount reported under field 51 (i.e. field 52 is an "of which" field of 51). Arrears of
		interest, by contrast, are not part of this amount. Any past due or overdue late interest (interest which accrues on
		arrears) should be treated as arrears of interest. Total debt outstanding at the end of the year is defined as the sum
		of principal disbursed and still outstanding and arrears of interest.
	</entry>

	<entry key="53arrearsOfInterest.label">53. Arrears of Interest</entry>
	<entry key="53arrearsOfInterest.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="53arrearsOfInterest.help">At the end of the year (in full amount)</entry>
	<entry key="53arrearsOfInterest.help.detail">Field no. 53 - Arrears of interest: Report separately any arrears of principal and interest at the end
		of the reporting year, taking into account debt service payments received during the year (amortisation under field 35
		and interest received under field 50), and including arrears that have arisen during the reporting year. Arrears of
		principal are part of the principal owed on the loan and should be included in the amount reported under field 51
		(i.e. field 52 is an "of which" field of 51). Arrears of interest, by contrast, are not part of this amount. Any past
		due or overdue late interest (interest which accrues on arrears) should be treated as arrears of interest. Total debt
		outstanding at the end of the year is defined as the sum of principal disbursed and still outstanding and arrears of
		interest.</entry>
</properties>
