<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- ~ Copyright (c) 2013 Development Gateway. ~ All rights reserved. This program and the accompanying materials ~ are made 
	available under the terms of the GNU Public License v3.0 ~ which accompanies this distribution, and is available at ~ http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl.html -->

<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
	<entry key="16geographicalTargetArea.label">Geographical Target Area</entry>
	<entry key="16geographicalTargetArea.placeholder">Maximum 100 characters.</entry>
	<entry key="16geographicalTargetArea.help">Field no. 16 - Geographical target area</entry>
	<entry key="16geographicalTargetArea.help.detail"> Specify the area (town, region) in the recipient country that is intended to benefit from the
		activity. Specify the recipient countries if the activity benefits several recipients.</entry>

	<entry key="17startingDate.label">Starting Date</entry>
	<entry key="17startingDate.placeholder">Enter in text format DD-MM-YYYY</entry>
	<entry key="17startingDate.help">Field no. 17 - Starting date (actual/expected)</entry>
	<entry key="17startingDate.help.detail"> The expected starting and completion dates allow identification of activities being implemented at
		any point of time.</entry>

	<entry key="18completionDate.label">Completion Date</entry>
	<entry key="18completionDate.placeholder">Enter in text format DD-MM-YYYY</entry>
	<entry key="18completionDate.help">Field no. 18 - Completion date (actual/expected)</entry>
	<entry key="18completionDate.help.detail">The expected starting and completion dates allow identification of activities being implemented at any
		point of time.</entry>

	<entry key="19description.label">Description</entry>
	<entry key="19description.placeholder">No limitation of length</entry>
	<entry key="19description.help">Field no. 19 - Project description</entry>
	<entry key="19description.help.detail">Many agencies’ databases contain project summaries or descriptions of the main objectives of the
		activity. These can be included in the CRS++ database in a text field of unrestricted length. The information permits
		the Secretariat to check the accuracy and consistency of purpose coding. In addition, descriptive information is
		valuable in detailed sectoral studies, and allows users to make research on topics (sectors or themes) not separately
		identified in existing classifications (e.g. disability), using keyword searches.
	</entry>

	<entry key="policyObjectives.label">Policy Objectives</entry>

	<entry key="20genderEquality.label">Gender Equality</entry>
	<entry key="20genderEquality.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="20genderEquality.help">Field no. 20 - Gender equality</entry>
	<entry key="20genderEquality.help.detail">Principal policy objectives are those which can be identified as being fundamental in the design and
		impact of the activity and which are an explicit objective of the activity. They may be selected by answering the
		question “would the activity have been undertaken without this objective?”. Significant policy objectives are those
		which, although important, were not the prime motivation for undertaking the activity. The score “not targeted” means
		that the activity was found not to target the policy objective. Leave the field blank if the activity has not been
		screened against the objective. More information on this policy marker is available in Annex 17 of the CRS++
		Gudielines available at http://www.oecd.org/dac/stats/documentupload/DCD-DAC(2013)15-ADD2-FINAL-ENG.pdf (page 34);
		2=principal objective
		1=significant objective
		0=not targeted
		Blank=not screened</entry>

	<entry key="21aidToEnvironment.label">Aid to Environment</entry>
	<entry key="21aidToEnvironment.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="21aidToEnvironment.help">Field no. 21 - Aid to environment</entry>
	<entry key="21aidToEnvironment.help.detail">Principal policy objectives are those which can be identified as
		being fundamental in the design and
		impact of the activity and which are an explicit objective of the activity. They
		may be selected by answering the
		question “would the activity have been undertaken without this objective?”.
		Significant policy objectives are those
		which, although important, were not the prime motivation for undertaking the
		activity. The score “not targeted” means
		that the activity was found not to target the policy objective. Leave the
		field blank if the activity has not been
		screened against the objective. More information on this policy marker is
		available in Annex 17 of the CRS++ Gudielines
		available at
		http://www.oecd.org/dac/stats/documentupload/DCD-DAC(2013)15-ADD2-FINAL-ENG.pdf (page 34);2=principal
		objective;1=significant objective;;0=not targeted;Blank=not screened
	</entry>

	<entry key="22pdGg.label">PD/GG</entry>
	<entry key="22pdGg.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="22pdGg.help.detail">Field no. 22 - PD/GG (participatory development/good governance)</entry>
	<entry key="22pdGg.help.detail">Principal policy objectives are those which can be identified as being fundamental in the design and
		impact of the activity and which are an explicit objective of the activity. They may be selected by answering the
		question “would the activity have been undertaken without this objective?”. Significant policy objectives are those
		which, although important, were not the prime motivation for undertaking the activity. The score “not targeted” means
		that the activity was found not to target the policy objective. Leave the field blank if the activity has not been
		screened against the objective. More information on this policy marker is available in Annex 17 of the CRS++
		Gudielines available at http://www.oecd.org/dac/stats/documentupload/DCD-DAC(2013)15-ADD2-FINAL-ENG.pdf (page 34)</entry>

	<entry key="23tradeDevelopment.label">Trade Development</entry>
	<entry key="23tradeDevelopment.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="23tradeDevelopment.help">Field no. 23 - Trade development</entry>
	<entry key="23tradeDevelopment.help.detail">Principal policy objectives are those which can be identified as being fundamental in the design and
		impact of the activity and which are an explicit objective of the activity. They may be selected by answering the
		question “would the activity have been undertaken without this objective?”. Significant policy objectives are those
		which, although important, were not the prime motivation for undertaking the activity. The score “not targeted” means
		that the activity was found not to target the policy objective. Leave the field blank if the activity has not been
		screened against the objective. More information on this policy marker is available in Annex 17 of the CRS++
		Gudielines available at http://www.oecd.org/dac/stats/documentupload/DCD-DAC(2013)15-ADD2-FINAL-ENG.pdf (page 34)</entry>

	<entry key="typeOfAid.label">Type of Aid</entry>

	<entry key="24freestandingTechnicalCooperation.label">Free-standing Technical Cooperation</entry>
	<entry key="24freestandingTechnicalCooperation.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="24freestandingTechnicalCooperation.help">Field no. 24 - Free-standing Technical Assistance (FTC)</entry>
	<entry key="24freestandingTechnicalCooperation.help.detail">The FTC flag applies to type of aid C01
		“Project-type interventions” and, by default, to categories
		D01-D02 and E01-E02. FTC comprises activities whose
		primary purpose is to augment the level of knowledge, skills,
		technical know-how or productive aptitudes of the
		population of developing countries, i.e. increasing their stock of
		human intellectual capital, or their capacity for
		more effective use of their existing factor endowment. This relates
		essentially to activities that either enhance or
		supply human resources. It includes financing of students and trainees
		who are nationals of developing countries;
		experts, teachers, and volunteers; equipment and materials for training;
		research; development-oriented social and
		cultural programmes, etc. Associated supplies are also classified as
		technical co-operation.
	</entry>

	<entry key="25programmeBasedApproach.label">Program-based Approach</entry>
	<entry key="25programmeBasedApproach.placeholder">1=Yes or Blank</entry>
	<entry key="25programmeBasedApproach.help">Field no. 25 - Program-Based Approach (PBA)</entry>
	<entry key="25programmeBasedApproach.help.detail">They are a way of engaging in development co-operation based on the principles of co-ordinated support
		for a locally-owned programme of development, such as a national development strategy, a sector programme, a thematic
		programme or a programme of a specific organisation. Donors can support and implement programme-based approaches in
		different ways and across a range of aid modalities including budget support, sector budget support, project support,
		pooled arrangements and trust funds. For an activity to qualify as PBA, all four of the following tests must be met:
		A) The host country or organisation is exercising leadership over the programme supported by donors; B) A single
		comprehensive programme and budget framework is used; C) There is a formal process for donor co-ordination and
		harmonisation of donor procedures for at least two of the following systems: (i) reporting, (ii) budgeting, (iii)
		financial management and (iv) procurement; D) Support to the programme uses at least two of the following local
		systems: (i) programme design, (ii) programme implementation, (iii) financial management and (iv) monitoring and
		evaluation.</entry>

	<entry key="26investmentProject.label">Investment Project</entry>
	<entry key="26investmentProject.placeholder">1=Yes or Blank</entry>
	<entry key="26investmentProject.help">Field no. 26 - Investment</entry>
	<entry key="26investmentProject.help.detail">Activities flagged as investment comprise a) schemes to increase and/or improve the recipient’s stock
		of physical capital and b) financing the supply of goods and services in support of such schemes. Most activities
		assigned the “investment” flag are classified as type of aid C01 “Project-type interventions”.</entry>

	<entry key="27associatedFinancing.label">Associated Financing</entry>
	<entry key="27associatedFinancing.placeholder">1=Yes or Blank</entry>
	<entry key="27associatedFinancing.help">Field no. 27 - Associated Financing (AF)</entry>
	<entry key="27associatedFinancing.help.detail">The combination of ODA, whether grants or loans, with any other funding to form finance packages. AF
		associates two or more of the following, at least one of which is in effect tied or partially untied: i) official
		development assistance; ii) other official flows with a grant element of at least 25 per cent; iii) officially
		supported export credits, other official flows or other funds with a grant element of less than 25 per cent. In an
		associated financing package, the availability of concessional funds is conditional upon acceptance of the linked
		non-concessional component.</entry>

	<entry key="rioMarkers.label">Rio Markers</entry>

	<entry key="28biodiversity.label">Biodiversity</entry>
	<entry key="28biodiversity.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="28biodiversity.help">Field no. 28 - Biodiversity</entry>
	<entry key="28biodiversity.help.detail">The marker allows for the identification of activities that target the
		objectives of the Rio United
		Nations Convention on Biological Diversity (UNCBD). Principal policy objectives are those
		which can be identified as
		being fundamental in the design and impact of the activity and which are an explicit
		objective of the activity. They
		may be selected by answering the question “would the activity have been undertaken
		without this objective?”.
		Significant policy objectives are those which, although important, were not the prime
		motivation for undertaking the
		activity. The score “not targeted” means that the activity was found not to target the
		policy objective. Leave the
		field blank if the activity has not been screened against the objective. The definition of
		this Rio marker, its
		background , some examples and FAQs are given in Annex 18 of the CRS++ Gudieliens available at
		http://www.oecd.org/dac/stats/documentupload/DCD-DAC(2013)15-ADD2-FINAL-ENG.pdf (page 43).</entry>

	<entry key="29ccMitigation.label">Climate Change - Mitigation</entry>
	<entry key="29ccMitigation.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="29ccMitigation.help">Field no. 29 - Climate Change - Mitigation</entry>
	<entry key="29ccMitigation.help.detail">The marker allows for the identification of activities that target the objectives of the Rio United
		Nations Framework Convention on Climate Change (UNFCCC) with distinct markers for adaptation and mitigation. Principal
		policy objectives are those which can be identified as being fundamental in the design and impact of the activity and
		which are an explicit objective of the activity. They may be selected by answering the question “would the activity
		have been undertaken without this objective?”. Significant policy objectives are those which, although important, were
		not the prime motivation for undertaking the activity. The score “not targeted” means that the activity was found not
		to target the policy objective. Leave the field blank if the activity has not been screened against the objective. The
		definition of this Rio marker, its background , some examples and FAQs are given in Annex 18 of the CRS++ Gudieliens
		available at http://www.oecd.org/dac/stats/documentupload/DCD-DAC(2013)15-ADD2-FINAL-ENG.pdf (page 43).</entry>

	<entry key="30ccAdaptation.label">Climate Change - Adaptation</entry>
	<entry key="30ccAdaptation.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="30ccAdaptation.help">Field no. 30 - Climate Change - Adaptation</entry>
	<entry key="30ccAdaptation.help.detail">The marker allows for the identification of activities that target the objectives of the Rio United
		Nations Framework Convention on Climate Change (UNFCCC) with distinct markers for adaptation and mitigation. Principal
		policy objectives are those which can be identified as being fundamental in the design and impact of the activity and
		which are an explicit objective of the activity. They may be selected by answering the question “would the activity
		have been undertaken without this objective?”. Significant policy objectives are those which, although important, were
		not the prime motivation for undertaking the activity. The score “not targeted” means that the activity was found not
		to target the policy objective. Leave the field blank if the activity has not been screened against the objective. The
		definition of this Rio marker, its background , some examples and FAQs are given in Annex 18 of the CRS++ Gudieliens
		available at http://www.oecd.org/dac/stats/documentupload/DCD-DAC(2013)15-ADD2-FINAL-ENG.pdf (page 43)</entry>

	<entry key="31desertification.label">Desertification</entry>
	<entry key="31desertification.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="31desertification.help">Field no. 31 - Desertification</entry>
	<entry key="31desertification.help.detail">The marker allows for the identification of activities that target the
		objectives of the Rio United Nations Convention to Combat Desertification (UNCCD). Principal policy objectives are
		those which can be identified as being fundamental in the design and impact of the activity and which are an explicit
		objective of the activity (a score “3” instead of "2" is used to separately identify activities in support of
		national, sub-regional or regional action programmes). They may be selected by answering the question “would the
		activity have been undertaken without this objective?”. Significant policy objectives are those which, although
		important, were not the prime motivation for undertaking the activity. The score “not targeted” means that the
		activity was found not to target the policy objective. Leave the field blank if the activity has not been screened
		against the objective. The definition of this Rio marker, its background , some examples and FAQs are given in Annex
		18 of the CRS++ Guidelines available at
		http://www.oecd.org/dac/stats/documentupload/DCD-DAC(2013)15-ADD2-FINAL-ENG.pdf (page 43).</entry>
</properties>
