<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- ~ Copyright (c) 2013 Development Gateway. ~ All rights reserved. This program and the accompanying materials ~ are made 
	available under the terms of the GNU Public License v3.0 ~ which accompanies this distribution, and is available at ~ http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl.html -->

<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
	<entry key="32currency.label">32. National Ccurrency</entry>
	<entry key="32currency.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="32currency.help">Enter your national currency</entry>
	<entry key="32currency.help.detail">Field no. 32 - National Ccurrency: Enter your national currency</entry>

	<entry key="33commitments.label">33. Commitments</entry>
	<entry key="33commitments.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="33commitments.help">New amounts committed during the reporting year (full amount)</entry>
	<entry key="33commitments.help.detail">Field no. 33 - Commitments: New amounts committed during the reporting year. The amount for the
		initial commitment taking account of any revisions of the commitment that occurred
		during the year. After the original
		commitment year, report only the annual increases (net amounts added to earlier
		years commitments) or decreases (net
		reductions in earlier year's commitments). The recording of cancellations on
		earlier years commitments is allowed, but
		only in the form of an aggregate ("bilateral, unspecified/sector,
		unspecified"). For multilateral contributions,
		commitments show the total amounts of multi-year agreements with
		multilateral institutions. For capital subscriptions
		in the form of notes encashable at sight, enter the total
		expected amount of deposits of such notes as the amount
		committed. Report only one (positive or negative) amount for
		each activity. Commitments are considered to be made at
		the date a loan or grant agreement is signed or the obligation
		is otherwise made known to the recipient (e.g. in the
		case of budgetary allocations, the final vote of the budget
		should be taken as the date of commitment). For certain
		special expenditures, e.g. humanitarian aid, the date of
		disbursement may be taken as the date of commitment. A
		commitment is a firm written obligation by a government or
		official agency, backed by the appropriation or availability
		of the necessary funds, to provide resources of a
		specified amount under specified financial terms and conditions and
		for specified purposes for the benefit of a
		recipient country or a multilateral agency.</entry>

	<entry key="34amountsExtended.label">34 Amounts Extended</entry>
	<entry key="34amountsExtended.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="34amountsExtended.help">Amount disbursed during the reporting year (full amount)</entry>
	<entry key="34amountsExtended.help.detail">Field no. 34 Amounts extended: Report the amount disbursed during the year. When reporting a
		disbursement on a former commitment, all CRS++ fields (except fields 36-40 and 42-49)
		should be completed, with field
		34. 'Amounts extended' indicating the amount disbursed, and field '33. Commitments
		being equal to 0'.</entry>


	<entry key="35amountsReceived.label">35. Amounts Received</entry>
	<entry key="35amountsReceived.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="35amountsReceived.help">Field no. 35 - Amounts received: Payments received from the aid recipient during the reporting year (for loans, only principal
		payments, including any payments of arrears of principal). NB: DO NOT enter a negative amount except for capital
		losses.
	</entry>
	<entry key="35amountsReceived.help.detail">Field no. 35 - Amounts received: Amounts received consist in recoveries on bilateral grants,
		amortisation of loans and recoveries on multilateral ODA grants and capital subscriptions. Amortisation relates to
		principal payments received from the borrowing country during the reporting year, including any payments of arrears of
		principal. For repayments on loans that have been rescheduled in previous years, report the types of aid, purpose
		codes and types of finance of the original loans. In case these cannot be identified, the field 13. Type of aid should
		be left empty, the field 12.Type of finance set to 410 and the field 15. Purpose code set to 99810. Do not use type of
		aid F01-Debt relief as this would distort statistics on net debt relief.
	</entry>


	<entry key="36amountUntied.label">36. Amount Untied</entry>
	<entry key="36amountUntied.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="36amountUntied.help">On a commitment basis, for new commitments only (full amount). Procurement authorised in all OECD
		countries and substantially all developing countries.</entry>
	<entry key="36amountUntied.help.detail">"Field no. 36 - Amount untied: On a commitment basis, for new commitments only (full amount).
		Procurement authorized in all OECD countries and substantially all
		developing countries. Detailed guidance on tying
		status reporting is given by type of aid in Annex 11 of the CRS++ Gudilines
		available at
		http://www.oecd.org/dac/stats/documentupload/DCD-DAC(2013)15-ADD1-FINAL-ENG.pdf (pages 63 to 68). Consult
		also Annex
		16. Tied aid disciplines and untying recommendation at
		http://www.oecd.org/dac/stats/documentupload/DCD-DAC(2013)15-ADD2-FINAL-ENG.pdf (page 14)."</entry>

	<entry key="37amountPartiallyUntied.label">37. Amount Partially Untied</entry>
	<entry key="37amountPartiallyUntied.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="37amountPartiallyUntied.help">On a commitment basis, for new commitments only (full amount). Procurement limited to donor and
		substantially all developing countries.</entry>
	<entry key="37amountPartiallyUntied.help.detail">Field no. 37 - Amount partially untied: Partially untied aid is defined as loans and grants which are
		tied, contractually or in effect, to procurement of goods and services from a restricted number of countries which
		must include substantially all developing countries and can include the donor country. Consult also Annex 16. Tied aid
		disciplines and untying recommendation at
		http://www.oecd.org/dac/stats/documentupload/DCD-DAC(2013)15-ADD2-FINAL-ENG.pdf (page 14).</entry>

	<entry key="38amountTied.label">38. Amount Tied</entry>
	<entry key="38amountTied.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="38amountTied.help">On a commitment basis, for new commitments only (full amount). Procurement that does not fall under
		the definitions of untied or partially untied aid.
	</entry>
	<entry key="38amountTied.help.detail">Field no. 38 - Amount tied: Transactions are considered tied unless the donor has, at the time of the
		aid offer, clearly specified a range of countries eligible for procurement which meets the tests for "untied" or
		"partially untied" aid. Consult also Annex 16. Tied aid disciplines and untying recommendation at
		http://www.oecd.org/dac/stats/documentupload/DCD-DAC(2013)15-ADD2-FINAL-ENG.pdf (page 14). For activities for which
		the tying status is reported, the sum of the amounts reported as untied, partially untied and tied should equal the
		total amount of these activities.
	</entry>

	<entry key="39amountOfIRTC.label">39. Amount of IRTC</entry>
	<entry key="39amountOfIRTC.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="39amountOfIRTC.help">For new commitments only, if investment (field 26)=1. Report in full amount</entry>
	<entry key="39amountOfIRTC.help.detail">Field no. 39 - Investment-Related Technical Assistance (IRTC): For new commitments only, if investment
		(field 26)=1. Report in full amount. Investment-related technical co-operation is defined as the financing of services
		by a donor country with the primary purpose of contributing to the design and/or implementation of a project or
		programme aiming to increase the physical capital stock of the recipient country. These services include consulting
		services, technical support, the provision of know-how linked to the execution of an investment project, and the
		contribution of the donors own personnel to the actual implementation of the project (managers, technicians, skilled
		labour etc.).</entry>

	<entry key="40amountOfExpertsCommitments.label">40. If project-type, amount of experts commitments</entry>
	<entry key="40amountOfExpertsCommitments.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="40amountOfExpertsCommitments.help">Optional reporting, if project-type (field 13 =C01)</entry>
	<entry key="40amountOfExpertsCommitments.help.detail">Field no. 40 - If project-type, amount of experts commitments: Optional reporting (full amount), if
		project-type (field 13 =C01). If you are able to do so, report the amount committed for financing donor
		experts/consultants.</entry>

	<entry key="41amountOfExpertsExtended.label">41. If project-type, amount of experts extended</entry>
	<entry key="41amountOfExpertsExtended.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="41amountOfExpertsExtended.help">Optional reporting, if project-type (field 13=C01).</entry>
	<entry key="41amountOfExpertsExtended.help.detail">Field no. 41 - If project-type, amount of experts extended: Optional reporting (full amount), if
		project-type (field 13 =C01). If you are able to do so, report the amount disbursed for financing donor
		experts/consultants.
	</entry>

	<entry key="42amountOfExportCredit.label">42. Amount of export credit in AF package</entry>
	<entry key="42amountOfExportCredit.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="42amountOfExportCredit.help">For commitments only (full amount), if AF (field 27=1). Use your national currency. </entry>
	<entry key="42amountOfExportCredit.help.detail">Field no. 42 - Amount of export credit in AF package: For commitments only (full amount), if AF (field 27=1). Use your national currency. 
        The sum of the amount committed (field 33) and the amount of export credit (field 42) equals the actual financial flow to the 
        recipient country i.e. the amount of the associated financing package. Use the description field (field 19) to give information 
        on any other funds injected in the package (e.g. private bank loans, contributions from private investors) and explain how the 
        components of the package are articulated.</entry>
</properties>
