<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- ~ Copyright (c) 2013 Development Gateway. ~ All rights reserved. This program and the accompanying materials ~ are made 
	available under the terms of the GNU Public License v3.0 ~ which accompanies this distribution, and is available at ~ http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl.html -->

<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
	<entry key="otherMarkers.label">Other Markers</entry>

	<entry key="32bOtherCurrency.label">32.b Other currency than national</entry>
	<entry key="32bOtherCurrency.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="32bOtherCurrency.help">Enter other currency than your national currency, if necessary</entry>
	<entry key="32bOtherCurrency.help.detail">Field no. 32b - Other currency than national: enter other currency than national in case the
		transaction is denominated in foreign currency (as per financial agreement or financial report)</entry>

	<entry key="32cExchangeRate.label">32.c Exchange rate indicated in financial documents</entry>
	<entry key="32cExchangeRate.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="32cExchangeRate.help">Enter exchange rates officially used in the transaction, if indicated in the financial agreement or
		report</entry>
	<entry key="32cExchangeRate.help.detail">Field no. 32c. Exchange rate indicated in financial documents (if any): it may be possible that the
		exchange rate for the transaction is indicated in the financial agreement or financial report attached to it. In this
		case indicate the applied exchange rate. If there is no specific exchange rate applied, leave this field blank
	</entry>

	<entry key="34bBudgetCode.label">34.b Budget Code</entry>
	<entry key="34bBudgetCode.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="34bBudgetCode.help">Insert the budget code under which resources were made available for this transaction.</entry>
	<entry key="34bBudgetCode.help.detail">Field no. 34.b - Budget code: refer to the budget appropriations and/or the monthly/quarterly cash
		plans for your agency and identify the budget code (or sub-code) under which resource were made available for this
		transaction. If there is no unique code for this transaction, include the one-higher budget code (or sib-code) which
		includes the transaction, among other initiatives
	</entry>

	<entry key="34cBudgetLine.label">34.c Budget Line</entry>
	<entry key="34cBudgetLine.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="34cBudgetLine.help">Insert the budget title under which resources were made available for this transaction.</entry>
	<entry key="34cBudgetLine.help.detail">Field no. 34.c - Budget title: refer to the budget appropriations and/or the monthly/quarterly cash
		plans for your agency and identify the budget title (or sub-title) under which resource were made available for this
		transaction. If there is no unique title for this transaction, include the one-higher budget title (or sub-title)
		which includes the transaction, among other initiatives. Most of the time the title is going to be an economic item,
		e.g. other recurrent expenditures titles or investment expenditures titles.
	</entry>

	<entry key="34dBudgetActivity.label">34.d Budget Activity</entry>
	<entry key="34dBudgetActivity.placeholder"></entry>
	<entry key="34dBudgetActivity.help">Insert the budget activity under which resources were made available for this transaction.
	</entry>
	<entry key="34dBudgetActivity.help.detail">Field no. 34.d - Budget code: refer to the budget appropriations and/or the monthly/quarterly cash
		plans for your agency and identify the budget activity under which resource were made available for this transaction.
		If there is no unique activity for this transaction, include the one-higher budget activity which includes the
		transaction, among other initiatives. In case your budget does not contain activity items, leave this filed blank.
		Activity items are to be found under budget programs when the budget is presented as a Program-Based Budget (PBB).
	</entry>

	<entry key="table.currentYear">Current Year</entry>
	<entry key="table.currentYearP1">Current Year + 1</entry>
	<entry key="table.currentYearP2">Current Year + 2</entry>
	<entry key="table.currentYearP3">Current Year + 3</entry>
	<entry key="table.currentYearP4">Current Year + 4</entry>
	<entry key="table.budgetMtef">Budget/MTEF</entry>
	<entry key="table.disbursement">Disbursement</entry>
	<entry key="table.code">Code</entry>
	<entry key="table.line">Line</entry>
	<entry key="table.activity">Activity</entry>

</properties>
